airdrops.io 2019-06-16

# Privacy & Cookie Policy » airdrops.io

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?  
**When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your email address or other details to help you with your experience. We may collect and process the following personal data in order to inform you about cryptocurrency airdrops:  
**      •** E-Mail  
**      •** Name  
**      •** IP address  
**      •** Ethereum address (in case an Ethereum address is considered as personal date in accordance with the applicable date protection law)  
**      •** Social media  
You will automatically sign up for the newsletter of airdrops.io and the newsletter of the projects that offers the airdrop if you join exclusive airdrops that are hosted on airdrops.io. We only share all submitted data on exclusive airdrop forms with the projects that offers the airdrop.

**When do we collect information?  
**We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?  
**We may use the information we collect from you when you register for an exclusive airdrop, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**•**  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**•**  To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.  
**      •** To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**•**  To verify that you are following the rules of our exclusive airdrops.

**How do we protect your information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

On the basis of the applicable data protection law you have several rights with regard to your personal data. The rights with regard to your personal data are explicitly defined in the applicable data protection law and are as follows:

**      • **You have the right to access your personal data;  
**      • **You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data;  
**      • **You have the right to withdraw your consent for the processing of your personal data;  
**      • **You have the right of rectification or erasure of your personal data;  
**      • **You have the right of restriction of the processing of your personal data(in some cases);  
**      • **You have the right to lodge a complaint with a Data Protection Authority;  
**      • **You have the right to data portability.

The right to data portability is your right to receive your personal data that you provided to us in a structured and commonly used format and the right to transmit such data to another “controller”. The definition of “controller” is set forth in applicable data protection law. We will not hinder you if you want to transmit your personal data. If it is technically possible we will transmit your personal data directly to another controller at your request.

If you wish to exercise your rights with regard to your personal data please let us know. We can be reached by email: mail@airdrops.io.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?  
**Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

**•**  Keep track of advertisements.

**•**  Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

**Third-party disclosure  
**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links  
**Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google  
**Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

**•**  Remarketing with Google AdSense

**•**  Google Display Network Impression Reporting

**•**  Demographics and Interests Reporting

**•**  DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?  
**We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?  
**It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)  
**When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Do we let third-parties, including ad networks or plug-ins collect PII from children under 13?

**Fair Information Practices  
**The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
**We will notify you via email  
**•**  Within 7 business days  
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**We collect your email address in order to:  
****      •** Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions  
**      •** Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

****If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can simply unsubscribe:  
****      **•**  We will remove you from our mailing list and our database if you click the unsubscribe link in our newsletter mails.

**Contact & Identity  
**If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Andreas L.
